If you're relocating to Fort Hood or any
of the surrounding areas [music]
and you want space, value, and lowered
monthly costs, this home [music] is
listed at just $363,000.
Hi, I'm Andrea Dudik with Living in
Central Texas, and today we're touring
one of my newest listings in Colleen,
Texas. [music]
It's just 14 minutes away from Fort Hood
and 5 minutes from Satan Medical Center.
This home [music] is absolutely
beautiful with so much curb appeal. It's
[music] listed at $363,000.
It features a four bed, 2 and a half
bath [music]
with a designated office space and an
office nook. [music] and it has some
really awesome add value features that a
lot of buyers are looking for. Let's
take a look.
With [music] over 2500 square ft, this
home offers a flexible layout that works
beautifully for everyday living,
entertaining, and working from home.
[music] I'm telling you, this home feels
massive and so much bigger than the 2500
square [music] foot state.
This kitchen features a large walk-in
[music] pantry, ample storage, there are
so many cabinets, and opens nicely to
the living area. It's [music] super
functional and welcoming.
office space/flex [music]
room.
Office nook.
[music]
This mud bench area is perfect for
shoes, backpacks, [music] and everyday
gear. It's simple, it's practical, it's
so useful, and it's super cute. The
primary [music] suite is absolutely
fantastic. I love the lighting and
overall layout of this [music] space.
It features dual closets, a separate
soaking tub and shower, and plenty
[music] of space to unwind.
The home also includes a paidoff water
[music] softener, adding comfort and
protecting your plumbing and appliances.
These solar panels are fully paid off,
[music] meaning lower electric bills
with no solar loan to assume. A huge
long-term saving advantage.
And of course, as I mentioned before,
this home is so [music] close to Fort
Hood, just 14 minutes away. And with
easy access to shopping, dining, and
daily conveniences, making it an [music]
excellent option for military families
or anyone wanting space without
restrictions.
If you're looking for a movein ready
home, [music]
14 minutes from Fort Hood, minutes from
Satan Medical Center with paid off
solar, paid off water [music] softener,
and plenty of space to grow, you'll want
to see this one in person. And if you
are relocating to the central Texas area
[music]
or would like to schedule a private tour
of this home, reach out anytime. [music]
Don't forget to like and subscribe for
more home tours and relocation tips here
in the central Texas area. Till next
time.